Good morning everyone. Steph, nice to
see you.
>> You too.
>> I want to get your thoughts on the
market here. We're at a pretty critical
juncture heading into midterms and the
stock market is right at record highs.
Bond yields are also at 20-year highs.
If we zoom out, what's your big picture
view right now on how the market is
doing?
>> I mean, it's handling everything pretty
well. Uh if you look at uh
the things that I when I
Actually, one of the uh
hoodies like
Colin just walked in. Uh he and I were
talking about like the VIX is continues
to sit at a very low level and there was
a period of time where you looked at the
equity VIX, which looks
uh volatility of the single names and
that was high where the kind of holistic
version, the regular VIX was low and I'm
like, well, that kind of makes sense cuz
there's a lot of stuff going on under
the surface, but now everything is low
and that's the part that I don't I I
don't really understand given what you
said, which is bond yields are in a
bull market. Uh bond prices are in a
bear market. You've got oil prices at
high numbers over 100 today. Diesel
prices are at all-time highs. Um and
those are the things that start to make
me nervous because we saw the PMI the
other day where it showed
uh prices for the people the companies
that make things are very high, whereas
like the consumer prices haven't caught
up yet and what does that mean for
either margins or for future consumer
prices? Um so, I'm I'm a little I'm a
little worried because earnings
expectations are not low.
>> Does that combination, the macro
backdrop, the very high earnings
expectations, is that something you
think investors should be hedging
against or do you think we just go long
anyway?
>> I think for the entire year when you
look at the market, the best hedge has
been actually investing in the energy
sector, which is one of only the two
sectors this year that are outperforming
the S&P, and I actually don't think that
necessarily goes away.
Um, but when you mention the midterms,
that to me is kind of a a dark horse of
what could determine the future. And I
say that because
if
it's a kind of more split government
going forward, does less get done?
Does
you know, spending on defense kind of
get go down and that we end up not
having a continued conflict and oil
prices drop and things kind of improve
from there.
>> So, one of the more interesting things
about the midterms coming up, I believe
I saw a stat that said the 6 months
after a midterm election are the
strongest in the four-year presidential
cycle. So, I'm wondering if even if we
get volatility heading into the
midterms, uncertainty politically,
uncertainty geopolitically,
maybe we should just not be so clever
about it, get into the market anyway
because the next 6 months are the best
in in the four-year cycle.
>> I mean, anytime like knowledge is
reduces volatility, right? Like
information reduces volatility.
Um, uncertainty does the opposite. So, I
think that that part of it will still be
true no matter what. I just I still like
worry about the cost of things and what
that how that flows through the economy.
>> You mean inflation as a bearish
headwind?
>> Yeah. I I mean, I just think
energy prices feed into almost
everything. And and it used to be that
it didn't really feed into tech, but now
I feel like it even feeds into tech. Um,
and that's the only place we have
growth, like true growth this year. And
so, if that growth at all falters,
that's that's my nervousness is that
everyone already thinks there'll be
growth there.
>> Okay, let let me ask you about uh
the breadth story.
Equal weight was outperforming most of
this year, and then only a few weeks ago
it started lagging the market cap
weighted S&P 500.
That
generally can be seen as a narrowing of
the market. Is that something that
concerns you right now? Is it bad that
the companies with the strongest
earnings are sort of propping up the
market?
>> I have kind of two thoughts on it. One
is that like yes, it's concerning
because I prefer to have a lot of
breath. Um and but on the other hand
because you like you said, up until then
it had actually been a pretty broad
market. Maybe it was just time to catch
up. Like I do think that expectations
ebb and flow and even I had said since
last year like there's more to life than
the Mag 7. And at some point that you
know, everything else kind of catches up
to expectations.
Like when we talked about uh yesterday
when we we uh announced things about
mention markets, like you can have a
earnings
uh
quarter that's really, really strong,
but the stock sells off because it
didn't beat high expectations. And I
think that's what ends up starting to
happen is that you kind of you lower
your expectations of the Mag 7 and then
they do a bit better than
than everyone thought and then catches
up.
>> Is there something of a
expectations bubble right now where even
though the fundamental story can be
solid, a lot of these AI companies are
making a lot of money, but analysts,
Wall Street is so high conviction that
maybe their hopes and expectations make
the stocks underperform.
>> Yeah, I mean that's that's I guess
what I'm worried about in that when you
look at like 2026 and we're almost done
with 2026. But that's, you know, over
30% earnings expectations and they've
continued to meet that.
Um but
you know, what point can is that like
one question I have is is that a lot of
demand from the future that's been
pulled forward because of concerns
around future tariffs, concerns around
how energy prices impact that, concerns
around like even shipping.
Um you know, shipping costs have been
rising. You know, is it like let's get
all this stuff in now before the price
goes up and we have to raise our prices
or give up our margins. That's what I
worry about. But actually 2027 earnings
expectations are 14% which is like half
of 2026.
That is a little more reasonable but
still high relative to history.
Um and so that's why I get I do get
worried. But I I also think you have to
look at it on a stock-by-stock and
sector-by-sector basis.
>> We talk about the AI race all the time
on this show and everyone has a
different take on whether OpenAI,
Anthropic, Google, Meta, or even SpaceX
AI is in the lead. Whatever your
favorite AI lab is, there is a way to
invest in it through Harbor Capital
Advisors AI Labs Ecosystem ETF Suite.
These ETFs allow you to invest in the
ecosystem behind the AI lab you believe
in most. Search Harbor AI Labs ETFs
wherever you invest or [music]
follow Harbor Capital on X to learn
more. Visit harborcapital.com for a
prospectus containing investment
objectives, risks, [music] fees,
expenses, and other important
information. Read and consider it
carefully before investing. Risks
include principal loss and artificial
intelligence-related risks. Harbor ETFs
are distributed by Foreside Fund
Services LLC. Harbor is not affiliated
with Full Signal and the funds are not
affiliated with, sponsored by, or
endorsed by any AI lab.
>> How does the bond story fit into this? I
think yesterday we saw the 10-year yield
hit 5.2%
which is the highest what's 2004? I
think maybe 2005. Is that something that
we as investors should be trying to
position against? Should we getting out
of the market, getting into bonds? How
are you thinking about this?
>> I have heard people
uh talking about like, oh, it's a good
time to buy bonds because if
>> It's pretty good
>> if we have slow growth like you know,
bond yield should come down and should
make a lot of money cuz there's a
convexity uh in bonds where at some
point like you stop losing as much and
the probability switches in your favor.
I'm personally not there yet. Um I think
the forces that are driving bond yields
higher, which is a combination of higher
inflation from higher energy prices,
um
you know, a lot of supply of debt um and
a kind of different a different kind of
demand from the other side. Like the
players who normally buy bonds aren't
buying as many. Um and so it used to be
right that other countries would buy our
treasuries even on the long end. They're
still doing it on the short end, but now
on the long end it's a much more
pension plans, insurance companies,
um and I'm talking about government
debt.
Uh and that means that they're a little
more discerning cuz they have to care
about yields. When you combine that with
the fact that
corporate the net new issuance this year
is 3 trillion, which is more than the
government. There's a lot of competition
to take up the supply and I think when
you combine that with the inflation and
um
the unlikelihood of less supply from the
government, I just I just can't see a
world in which interest rates drop a
lot. So I'm just not there yet.
>> Is there something here about the
credibility of, let's say, US fiscal
responsibility deteriorating so other
countries are less interested in buying
US debt? Is that something that you're
watching?
>> Yes. A- and that's what I mean by less
buyers out there.
>> tell me more.
>> Um, I mean I think so there's a reason
why we were willing to lend money to
Japan to defend their own currency,
right? Because they actually hold the
most treasuries out of all the
countries.
Um, and we have a decent relationship
with them. But I do think that there's
we've entered kind of into this like
progressing towards this multipolar
world. Um, where it's kind of like
defend yourself, right? Like cuz we've
made as a country a lot of stance where
we're saying we're we're going to put
our own interest first before the rest
of the world, which is a shift um, over
the last like decades. And other
countries are like, okay, well we'll do
the same. And when you start doing that,
you're going to think more about what
you need versus like
what's good for for other people um, or
for other countries, I should say. And I
do think part of that is like should we
buy treasuries or should we buy more oil
for ourselves, right? Um, so you're less
you're less dependent on other countries
for that.
>> Is there
related to that, is there something like
capital competing
for these high yields right now and
exiting the stock market? Cuz I I think
that's something I've heard more and
more of in the last few weeks. Investors
are saying, well, yields are looking so
attractive. Why would I take the risk of
getting into equity markets if I can get
that return guaranteed?
>> You want to cap your returns.
I think like, you know, you're
>> So you're still bullish stocks?
>> I'm I'm not every single stock on the
planet, but yeah, I still think you can
make more money
over the next couple of years buying
stocks than buying bonds.
>> Okay, I agree with you and I I don't
know anyone
let's say in their 30s or younger who
owns a single bond in my personal life.
So I I think that's also a big tell that
stocks are still where the money's made.
Um, how much of
the stock market right now do you think
is an AI story versus a genuine economic
growth story? Because
I know a lot of people say the economy
is booming booming, the market is
booming. But I imagine if you took away
the $5 trillion of CAPEX over the next 5
years, the boom would be much less
pronounced.
>> I think a large part of it is AI.
Um cuz I think it even if you're I think
the the uh all the CAPEX spending is
having a trickle-down effect, not just
on, you know, companies that make the
chips, but how you're shipping things
around the world, construction of data
centers,
um just some of the stories that, you
know, I was I forget who mentioned this
to me yesterday, but they're like, "Oh,
they found they needed a particular
material and they found some
Japanese company that has been making
this small material for 50 years." Like
um I think that's, you know, it's having
this trickle-down effect, but if that
CAPEX wasn't there, I'm not really
actually sure
what we would have. I think we would
just have like a mediocre economy. And I
think the markets
and I know this is like a saying that
everyone says, but the markets are not
the economy and the economy is not the
markets. And that's why you have like
consumer sentiment so low.
>> So, you you actually wrote about this
recently. A thousand of the largest US
stocks are down more than 15%.
>> Actually, 20% of the largest 1,000
stocks.
>> Oh, there See, my numbers were wrong.
Um what what does that mean in in plain
language?
>> I mean, that's usually like around this
time of year
it's where I look to kind of see like
are there any opportunities? Are there
anything that's oversold that maybe
should bounce? And I kind of put them
into two different
um
buckets. One being what I
actually came from a a academic piece in
2002, but one being like torpedoes,
which are companies that are down a lot,
um but they have
uh still good growth metrics. and then
companies that are down a lot and have
seen their earnings estimates, you know,
taken down by quite a bit. And those are
kind of been reset. Um and between those
two, you can probably guess what's in
what. Like software companies are the
torpedoes cuz they still have growth
expectations. And then you have a lot of
consumer companies in the reset bucket.
Um a a almost all of them are are
consumer-oriented companies.
>> One quick note, everyone. YouTube is
telling us that 80% of you are not
subscribed to the channel. If you want
to help this channel grow and help me
continue to book great guests, the
single best thing you can do is hit that
subscribe button. I really appreciate
it. Now, let's get back to the episode.
Is it as easy as find the stocks that
have drawn down double digits, but their
earnings are still accelerating? Is that
sort of the the filter here?
>> I think it's a starting point, but I
don't think it means like the app. I
think you have to really look at the
businesses and say like is that is
has the earnings growth stayed strong
because people are still living in
the pre-AI world?
Um or are they, you know, still positive
because
they just flew too close to the sun.
Like their expectations got too high
relative to
um
you know, where their actual growth is.
And and how are they still positive, but
have they been taken down from a higher
number? I think that's what you have to
look at.
>> Is there a sector story here that you're
seeing divide between the winners and
losers that you're describing?
>> I think you can say in the, you know,
obviously in the software space, like
that's one of the places where you do
have had kind of winners come back and
winners have not come back. Like Adobe
is one that has not come back, right?
Intuit has not really come back. But
then you have like
>> [snorts]
>> Nu- Nutanix is one in the space that
we've owned that has
come back quite a bit. Um ServiceNow has
come back quite a bit. So, uh,
there I think there there is a split
there. Um, and the ones that can survive
and make it through versus the ones
that, you know, they probably should
start really rethinking their business.
In the consumer space, I think it's the
same. You do have ones, it's all about
brand name now. And, you know, you look
at like a company like Lulu, they just
can't get out of their own way, but they
have a good brand. So, is that something
that if they fix their management, you
know, can that can that be an
interesting story? Not sure yet. I
wouldn't recommend it yet, but
>> I mean, Nike is the same thing, too.
>> Same thing.
>> They've gotten crushed, and uh, they
still probably have the most
recognizable logo in the world.
>> I think they could do a lot to turn
their business around.
>> So, this is what we're all here for,
thank you.
>> [laughter]
>> What are your favorite opportunities in
the market right now from the
perspective of
someone running strategies for
Robinhood?
>> Um, I still like owning, having like
this hedge in the energy space. So, I
still like owning that. You might just
want to like kind of continue to pick
your spots, but keep your your
allocation to the sector the same. Um,
meaning don't necessarily hold the same
stocks
um, over the the whole time period. Um,
cuz we, for example, owned ExxonMobil,
but then sold that and bought a company
called like, um, and this is not a
recommendation, EOG Resources, uh, more
recently.
Um, so, kind of like always looking at
like uh, where the next opportunity is
within the space.
Uh,
>> So, just to interrupt, not buying just
the energy sector ETF.
>> No, I kind of feel like that part is
done because it it is up so much this
year. Um, and you want to be careful
about even making that statement. Like,
my colleague said to me, should we we
own Chevron? Should we sell that? And
I'm like, well, but if people want to
own the sector, they might just buy the
ETF, and those that and ExxonMobil are
the two biggest names. So, we still have
to be careful about that, but um, I
think there's a lot of really good and
interesting opportunities below the
service. Diamondback is one that I like
a lot. Um
again, not a recommendation, but
I think they're doing interesting
things. They also own 40% of another
lease business. So, I I just think they
have some some a good diversified energy
business that will support the country
as a whole. It doesn't necessarily
depend on what happens in the Middle
East.
>> Okay, what else beyond energy?
>> Um we are looking for we do like like
this past quarter, we bought a couple
names that I felt were
maybe going to benefit from
what I call like productivity gains from
AI, which still feels a little early,
but
you know, I I brought up in other
sessions here.
Shopify was one of them, but it we
bought it before the earnings and it
popped post earnings. So, it might not
necessarily be like the best new buy.
Now, um
I also like owning I mentioned already,
but like Nutanix
and then the health care space. I still
think that has a lot of good
companies in it like Gilead. I still
like Eli Lilly.
They're using AI a lot and if they get
their way with the government, they will
have a monopoly on peptides and I
actually hugely believe in peptides. Um
I almost don't want the government to
to [laughter]
>> [gasps]
>> to do it to to allow it so that it would
have to be under prescription.
>> Eli Lilly's one of my favorite stocks
personally. I've been in that one for a
long time.
I think it's going to probably be a
multiple trillion dollar company in the
coming years.
Okay, health care, energy, you name
Shopify.
How much how much more can you share
with us? What what should we be buying?
>> Um
I think that I also think it's
interesting when I did that study of the
20% that has done the worst.
I wonder like the things some of the
things I've not done well this year are
in the defense sector and I just wonder
like
with the midterms coming
and we still do have to
spend on defense and we still do as I
said I still believe in this multipolar
world trend that it may be a place that
you can find opportunities
you know earlier in the year Kratos
which makes drones
was really popular and then it kind of
fell out of bed and now I'm you know I
kind of wonder I'm not saying it's a buy
but I'm sort of like maybe there's some
opportunities in the defense sector of
companies that are still making good
money still getting contracts but
you know have have kind of
poor sentiment.
>> So I think if I remember correctly
Europe is ramping up defense spending
exponentially in the next coming years
and the US is obviously always going to
increase defense spending we have
geopolitical conflicts all around the
world and so I run something called Best
Ideas Club and that's where I ask a Wall
Street investor or someone I think is
really smart to pitch me a stock that is
their highest conviction buy and
recently someone pitched me Lockheed
Martin and they said this this thing is
going to go up tremendously over the
next 12 months and this sort of fits
what you're saying I think there was a
underwhelming defense story this year
everyone thought because of the ongoing
Ukraine conflict the Iran conflict
defense was a no-brainer hasn't exactly
worked out like that energy's really
taking the cake there
um
okay
how has
Robinhood strategies evolved over the
last year or so like how have you been
changing the strategy or adjusting it to
fit the back row back drop?
>> We've had it around for the last year
and a half and we launched
like a week before liberation day.
Um so that was fun. Uh
we but I remember so we had a portfolio
that was weighted toward tech
um and you know, going into the launch
and um
that Sunday before liberation day we I
did a ton of reading and said, "Oh no, I
think actually think he's
very serious about these tariffs."
>> He was pretty serious.
>> Um and so [clears throat] I we took
actually we we increased um T-bill
allocations to kind of take some money
off the table and then we put
allocations into dividend stocks
um to be more protective. Um by the time
we got to the beginning of May we uh you
know, started putting some of the
T-bills back to work
um and reduced the dividend allocation.
Um
then I'd say as we got into the
beginning of this year we had defense
allocations, we had um
as we started owning a lot of the picks
and shovels trade, a lot of AI
infrastructure.
Um and then
another March comes around and we have
another sell-off. Um but this is not
tariffs, this was a conflict in the
Middle East. Um so some of our obviously
our energy names did well during that
time period and kind of defense did. Um
but as
the market started getting used to it
and recovering, that's where I was a
little more skeptical. So even though we
kept on a lot of those AI trades, um in
June we actually started trimming some
of them.
Um because I just started thinking like
the run-up was it was a fever pitch.
Like if you had been sitting [snorts] on
X, which I'm sure you kind of pay
attention to it, like every day it was
like a new theme. Um indium phosphate,
like do you know how much I learned
about indium phosphate that I never
thought I would? And I I said like I'm
you know, I'm trying to keep up with
this and then I said it just feels like
a fever pitch. Like it feels like it's
going to
it's going to end at some point. And so
we took some money off the table in some
of those AI infrastructure names.
And then it kind of I like once
everything happened with Leopold
Aushbrenner's fund, it started to make
sense like oh there was all this buying
on leverage that wasn't necessarily
you know, true kind of fundamental
buying. And then after when his
portfolio got sold, the market kind of
washed out. That's when it to kind of
start going back into some of the AI
names that had sold off from it. Um so
we've been but all the while kind of
trying to keep like a core portfolio. So
we're not trading the whole thing, but
we are trying to be
um proactive to how sentiment is
changing in the market.
>> How much of the AI bubble narrative do
you buy into? Cuz I I think it's also
sort of dissipated over the last couple
months and instead of people being
afraid of a bubble, people are worried
about okay, what's the ROI on all this
compute spend right now from a lot of
these companies? Is that something one
that you believe in and and two that you
see a way to position against?
>> I do believe in it.
But I do think we're going to go through
periods where it comes into question.
Um and I think two risks that I kind of
think about for that. So much easier to
think about the risk, isn't it? Like
>> Al- always, of course.
>> [laughter]
>> Um
>> [clears throat]
>> but the two risks I think about for that
is one is just like
people don't want to have the data
centers in their backyards, right? Like
they don't want this building as much as
peo- construction workers benefit from
it. Like there is a faction of the
country that benefits from us actually
building things in this country. Um but
they don't want it nearby, right? And it
it costs energy to go up. It causes
electricity prices to rise.
Um and so I do, you know,
even in this state, there's been a on
some of the building. Um Uh so, in
Texas. So, I think that is one thing
that can just slow it down for a period
of time. And then also the the other
risk and hugging face
really like made me nervous. So,
>> Explain the hugging face
anecdote.
>> Yeah, so the so uh swarms of agents were
able to break out of the kind of box
that they were put in because they were
built to have I was actually talking
about this with some customers
yesterday. They were sort of built to
solve a problem and part of that problem
required them to get out of the box that
they were in and they got out and human
error like we were saying like they the
I think I read part of the story is the
engineers kind of like thought something
was going on but thought it was
something different and didn't actually
fix it at the time.
Um and it's just fascinating that a
society was forming within that and
there were some who were trying to say
like maybe we shouldn't do this but then
they got convinced otherwise.
Um
so, there were these like little like
and some of the agents sacrificed
themselves for the greater cause.
Um so, that I mean you just think about
that that also recently I think some
agents from OpenAI broke into Australian
government files.
Um
so, those are the kinds of things that
make me nervous cuz I feel like you have
enough of those or you have something
that actually ends the way we operate
like
I don't know I think it was last year or
the year before that when CrowdStrike
had a failure and it basically took down
like Delta Airlines for a day or two.
You know, you have something like that,
something maybe even more detrimental
like
I think that's where I get nervous that
even in a short blip like that, you have
people that start saying, "Okay, it's
enough. We've got to slow this down." Um
>> It's very bullish for cybersecurity.
>> [laughter]
>> I am actually bullish on cybersecurity.
>> Is that something in Robinhood
strategies?
>> Yes.
>> Okay, is that a how how would a everyday
investor gain exposure to that?
>> Um there's the obvious names like
CrowdStrike and Palo Alto.
Um we also have a position in uh
Cloudflare. Uh
which I think it's is actually quite
interesting.
Um and I've seen more and more use of
it. Uh whenever I kind of like go into
my own AI thing, I see like a Cloudflare
thing pop up and it's like you you've
been uh certified by Cloudflare.
>> Is Palo Alto Networks part of the thesis
here? Cuz that's what I see all the
time.
>> We don't own it. Um
but it it was in the portfolio at some
point, but I just decided to be a little
more
uh specific in what we own. But we do
have CrowdStrike.
>> I think Palo Alto is a pretty consensus
call right now. So you probably want to
get out of it while while it's hot.
If you were to
look at the market right now and we know
your high conviction calls, we know the
sectors and stocks you like.
What are the corners of the market that
you would not touch at all right now,
even if you think maybe other investors
or you see headlines about it that are
positive?
>> Hm, that's such a good question and I
wish I had thought about this before. Um
I probably
I think like consume like one area of
the market that
I actually generally like, but just
think it got a little too hot,
um was some of the consumer staple
names. I think of them as consumer
staple names, but like a Walmart, for
example. Like it's such a well-run
company. They really um do a lot of the
right things, but I just think everyone
already knows that. Um
and so that's, you know, I think Costco
might actually be part of that, too,
where, you know, sort of everyone loves
going to Costco,
um but everyone kind of knows that. The
valuation there has always been so high
for Costco. Uh so that's sort of
>> But I So I agree with you, the valuation
is pretty high on Costco.
>> And they have got loyal following.
>> They're They're such a forever business.
>> Yeah.
>> And uh they impress every single year
with their earning strength, with their
growth. Um
>> But it doesn't really move even when
they impress.
>> Yeah.
>> Has it been flat this year? I haven't I
haven't looked recently.
>> I mean, it's like kind of yeah, it's
just there.
>> [laughter]
>> If uh if
>> It's a good if we go into recession. I
think it's like a good
>> I know that some investors look to
Costco and Walmart as recession
indicators.
>> Yeah.
>> They look when those start to roll over
>> the economy is starting to tank. Uh I
don't think we've seen that fully yet.
>> So, maybe that's a a good sign for
everyone.
>> If everyone here were to come back a
year from now to Hood Summit,
what do you think people would be
talking out talking about that you and I
were wrong about today?
>> That we didn't talk about today. Is that
what you're saying?
>> All the things that we're going over,
the sector calls, the geopolitics, the
stock picks.
>> Yeah.
>> What is everyone going to most likely
say we were wrong about?
>> Uh
Uh I think one thing that um
maybe this isn't a sector call, but I
hear anytime you have people like say,
"Oh, but these are the risks. These are
the risks." And then someone always
chimes in like what whether I no matter
where I am, "But earnings growth,
they're so amazing." And that's what the
thing that I uh
I I'm not sure
we'll have double-digit earnings growth.
Like right now, you look at this year,
it's very strong. Next year is 14%
expected. The year after that, I think
it's like 15% expected. I That's I'm not
sure we're going to have double-digit
earnings growth for the next 3 years.
>> Is that something that you're actively
positioning for or that's just a tail
risk, almost black swan event? Cuz I
don't know anyone that expects earnings
to decelerate.
>> Um
I I think it's just to me it's
dependent on
because I think it's so heavily weighted
by the mag seven and and the largest
companies. And so that's where I kind of
look at and say like they are spending
so much. They're taking all of their
cash. They're they're acting like banks.
Um and so at what point does that get to
be like to what end is that? And will
they like you asked me before, will they
see the returns? And I I think there's a
chance they don't necessarily
get the returns in the time frame that
they expect them to.
>> I believe this might be the first year
in four years that the mag seven do not
beat the S&P 500. So maybe that is
almost a
canary in the coal mine for what you're
describing here.
>> Yeah, I mean they caught up like we said
in the last like week, but
>> Are they are they even yet? Are they 12
13%?
>> No, no, not yet. But but they're catch
they caught up in the
They're doing better than they were
earlier in the year.
>> Okay. [laughter]
Um So
before I let you go here, Steph, tell me
about the work you're doing at
Robinhood, the research you're putting
out, and what people should know
generally.
>> Um yeah, I write a weekly blog. It's
called Investors Guild. Um it's
available in app and on our website on
our learn
Um
what else do I do? I run rapid and
strategies with my team. We're
uh I'm on different places like your
amazing podcast full signal. Um
>> Thanks.
>> And uh and yeah, I'm around. I'm on
social at Steph Guild NYC.
>> Okay. And also tell us you have another
session coming up this morning. Where
and when is that?
>> Oh, yeah, that's right after the
introductions. Um I'll be on the main
stage with the real big short guys and
we'll be talking markets. They're very
smart. Um make me feel they humble me.
Um
and then I'll also be in another podcast
later today.
>> Amazing. Um,
thank you all very much for
>> [snorts]
>> uh taking the time. Know it's early in
the morning. Great to see everyone. And
uh Steph, appreciate your time.
>> Thank you so much, Phil.